If you want to
grow a YouTube channel
that generates sales, views,
and leads, all you
need to do is
get water from this
side of a pipe
over a flame that's
constantly warming it so
that it turns to
steam and comes out
the other side. The
faster that water flows
through the pipe and
the hotter that flame
is, the faster and
better the results you
will have. Now, although
that sounds easy, there
is a big problem
because there are three
key sections on this
pipeline that can get
blocked, and if they
do, it completely wrecks
our results. So we
have the hardest section
to master here, that's
the YouTube section, and
that's how you get
views. This then drives
the viewers to the
second stage, which is
your marketing, and then
this then drives people
to the third stage,
which is your offer.
So all you have
to do to make
money and get views
is have water come
in one side and
come out the other
as steam. The thing
is, most people's pipe
looks like this, meaning
they can't get traffic
to their sales page,
their email, their marketing,
or their offer. Or
what does arrive is
just smoke. And then
others looks like this,
meaning views are flowing
into it, but a
few changes could completely
10x their sales. And
then of course we
have people like this,
and that's the mass
market, who can barely
turn the tap on
to get water into
the pipe in the
first place. So this
entire program is designed
to help you do
three things. One, find
the blocks. Two, fix
them. Three, warm viewers
up so they turn
into buyers. That is
literally all you have
to do to make
money and grow a
following on YouTube. So
now what I'm going
to do is I'm
going to give you
an overview. How this
entire system works, starting
with phase one. So
think of phase one
as a plumber coming
to your house just
to work out why
your pipe's blocked. Now
the first thing a
plumber will do to
try and diagnose a
problem isn't smashing your
kitchen apart with a
sledgehammer. They try a
really quick fix on
the block, like jamming
a bit of coat
hanger down it. And
then they turn the
tap on to see
if that worked. And
then if there's still
a block, then they
go much deeper and
take much larger actions,
like taking the kitchen
apart. So in phase
one. What we're going
to do is we're
going to try and
just get clarity on
what's potentially stopping the
water flowing through your
system right now. And
then we're going to
take a very few
small quick fixes and
make some minor changes
to your pipeline. And
then once we've done
that, we're just going
to drive some traffic
into it to see
if it has helped
or if we need
to do more work
and go much deeper
to get a result.
So then in phase
two, I'm going to
get you to post
a very simple video
that's going to teach
you the foundations of
the YouTube system. So
that's going to be
a little bit of
a challenge. Now, it
might get some people
into your pipeline, but
that's not what this
phase is about. This
phase is simply about
learning the foundations of
the system, so you
can then handle the
really advanced information that's
going to follow in
the next steps. Then
in phase three to
six, we're going to
go deeper on YouTube,
packaging, strategy, planning, writing
intros, and at the
end of that, you're
going to make three
to four more videos
using my system to
push more traffic into
the pipeline. And then
after that, in phase
two, it's going to
be a little bit
more complicated. seven, we're
going to look at
all of your new
data and ask where
in the pipe needs
our attention now. Once
we know that, you're
either just going to
keep posting videos because
the problem might still
be views, which is
going to be very
likely for many of
you because YouTube is
just 10 times harder
than anything else that
we do. Or you
move on to the
advanced modules and you
want to think of
these as like mini
courses that are there
to fix very specific
blockages in your pipeline.
So my system might
show you that the
real issue you have
is your sales page
isn't converting. So you'll
watch the offer module
and you're going to
write a new one
up and then we'll
drive some traffic at
it and we'll see
what happens. Or you
might realize that you
need a new high
ticket offer because you're
capped with your low
ticket one about how
much you can earn.
So you do the
high ticket launch module.
Or you might need
to just beef up
your email game. So
you follow my email
nurture system. Now I
have a lot of
options for you to
pick from in that
section. But Ed, can't
I just watch the
advanced modules and skip
all of the YouTube
stuff? I don't really
feel like that's my...
problem. Well, here's the
thing. So after 18
months of running this
program, I started to
ask, why is it
that some people seem
to come into this
and do so amazingly
well and find everything
easy and others struggle
and have more flops
within the business actions
they take? So I
went through tons of
my clients' data and
I discovered that the
people who did the
YouTube course first and
then posted a batch
of videos and then
did the advanced modules
nearly always had much
better results than those
that skipped it and
went to the advanced
modules. So I'm going
to show you some
examples of that in
a minute. So let's
get straight to the
business stuff. And when
I realized that it
actually made perfect sense
because everything that we
do in the initial
YouTube system prepares you
for those advanced modules
because you have to
learn how to talk
to your avatar, how
to make everything interesting
for them, how to
write, how to position
things in a way
that your viewers really
care about. So watching
the YouTube course first
makes you more of
an expert on what
your viewers actually care
about. So you can
then use that in
your marketing, which will
then turn viewers into
a more experienced person.
So I think that's
a great into buyers
more effectively. And if
you ignore the YouTube
content, everything else in
the advanced sections is
just going to be
so much harder for
you because you're going
to be missing all
of the skills that
I teach in it.
Also, when I rebuilt
this system, I did
so in a way
we use way more
AI. So you need
to build and refine
your custom AI coach,
which we do in
the YouTube course, so
that is then optimized
for running the business
side of things. So
if you're like, no,
Ed, I just want
to launch a high
ticket now, please don't
rush this. Stick to
the plan. We have
a very long time
together. And historically, everyone
who's come into this
and rushed just hasn't
had a great launch.
Okay, so with that
in mind, let's move
on to phase one,
which is about getting
clarity on your avatar,
your direction, your channel,
and your business. And
without this, we can't
make decisions that grow
our channel or business,
and people will get
totally stuck. By the
end of it, you're
going to be clear
on a few things.
How the views, sales,
and email system I've
built. What actually happens
to your views and
your channels when you
start doing this work,
so that you're mentally
prepared for what's about
to happen to you.
How YouTube growth actually
works, views, sales, and
leads, and what most
people totally misunderstand, and
how to position your
business channel and your
marketing so your pipeline
gets more viewers and
warms them up faster.
And then you're going
to do an audit
on your current business
and your channel and
your marketing using my
special audit system. So
you can see exactly
which of these three
areas in our pipeline
could be blocking your
views, sales, and email
from turning to steam
and coming out the
other end. And I
promise you, this is
going to be eye
-opening. When I did
this myself, I had
one of the biggest
light bulb moments of
all time. So I
cannot wait for you
to try this. And
then after that, based
on this discovery, you're
going to do some
minor adjustments to your
existing pipeline in the
three core stages to
see if we can
unblock it without having
to do a massive
overhaul of your existing
system.
And if you do
that, you're going to
be ahead of 99
% of the people
on YouTube, because most
don't even know half
of what I'm about
to teach you exists.
And getting this clarity
is the game changer.
So moving to the
next video, where I'm
going to give you
some clarity on what
this entire lead gen
and views system is,
how it works, and
why it's so flipping
powerful.